Gilang Alfi Syahri Ramadhan

 $Sidoarjo\ 61214\ |\ https://www.linkedin.com/in/gilang-ramaddhann/\ |\ 085156133161\ |\ gilangramaddhann@gmail.com/in/gilang-ramaddhann/\ |\ o85156133161\ |\ gilangramaddhann/\ |\ o85156133161\ |\ gilangramaddhann/\ |\ o85156133161\ |\ gilangramaddhann/\ |\ o85156133161\ |\ o8515613161\ |\ o85$

ABOUT ME

An undergraduate in System Information from Universitas Dinamika (Stikom Surabaya). UI/UX designer with more than 2 years of experience. During my work as a Freelancer in the field of UI/UX design, I have helped increase and attract users to be able to access web pages by redesigning or creating UI. Apart from that, I also work with front-end developers, back-end developers, and designers.

WORK EXPERIENCES

Lentera Fajar Indonesia

Front End Web Developer

(July 2022 - September 2022)

- Slicing UI components into code with React JS, Tailwind CSS, Gsap, and Scss.
- Create a system flow design to explain or describe every process that occurs in the program.
- Make a website that can see in a responsive design like mobile devices, tablets, and desktops.
- Testing the website performance and website speed with GtMetrix.
- Discuss with the backend web developer for creating dummy data to be applied in front.

UI Designer (July 2022 - September 2022)

- Hold discussions with representatives from Lentera Fajar Indonesia about what components will be implemented on the website.
- Discussion with any team that has been recorded or approved by Lentera Fajar Indonesia.
- Create wireframe UI like a landing page, about, article, school activity, and gallery.
- Create website UI.
- Perform Usability Testing Methods.
- Presented the results of the UI design to representatives of Lentera Fajar Indonesia.
- Received feedback from Lentera Fajar Indonesia.

Kinaya Group

Front End Web Developer

(March 2022 - April 2022)

- Discuss with UI/UX designer for creating a new UI website.
- Slicing UI Component into HTML5, CSS, SCSS, JavaScript, and TailwindCss.
- Creating a system flow design to explain or describe every process that occurs in the program.
- Testing the website performance and website speed with GtMetrix.

UI Designer (March 2022 - April 2022)

- Discuss with the clients about requirements users needed.
- Create wireframes UI guide.
- Create UI components such as landing pages, pages about the company, and information about the types of jobs that exist in the Kinaya Group.
- Making several design models which will then be presented to the Kinaya Group.
- Create a user manual or user guide to provide information on website pages so that users can run the website according to what was agreed during the interview

PT Anugrah Putra Kharisma

Fron-end Web Developer

(October 2020 - October 2020)

Designing UI for sales information and data information in the Dashboard component.

Slicing UI Dashboard into code with HTML 5, CSS, SCSS, Chart JS, JavaScript, and MySQL.

EDUCATION

Universitas Dinamika (Stikom Surabaya)

Bachelor System Information

(August 2018 - August 2022)

- Participated in inter-high school basketball championship committee activities in 2018 & 2019.
- Participated in the committee in the selection of campus BEM (Student Executive Body) 2019.
- Participated in a seminar on Personal Growth 2021.

PROJECTS

Lentera Fajar Indonesia

https://lenterafajarindonesia.sch.id/

(July 2022 - September 2022)

Lentera Fajar Indonesia is a Special School and they not using websites for promotion. In the progress of creating a website, especially as Frontend Web Developer, I'm using Figma for making a web design and prototyping after that I'm using React. Js for the front end.

Kinaya Group

https://kinayainterior.com/

(March 2022 - March 2022)

Me and my team entrusted with re-building company profiles from Kinaya Group (Architecture Company) starting with sketches (using Figma, Adobe Photoshop, and Adobe InDesign) and making responsive websites using HTML5, SASS, JavaScript, and TailwindCss.

SKILLS

Product Development Cycle, Interpersonal, Research and Development, Project Management, Content Writing, Leadership, English Speaking and Writing, Native Bahasa Indonesia.

CERTIFICATIONS

Intro To Data Analytics

RevoU

December 2022

Participate in activities to find out what a data analyst is, how important data analysts are, and how to properly manage the amount of data held by RevoU

Intro To Software Engineering

RevoU

December 2022

Participate in activities to knowing the other side of software engineering, the use of software engineering in companies, and the importance of software engineering in a company in the process of developing and growing business in the company.